fastladder.com 2012-05-25

# Fastladder : Privacy Policy

## Fastladder PRIVACY POLICY

livedoor Co., Ltd. (livedoor) will deal with users' personal information seriously observing the Act of the Protection of Personal Information and other relating laws and guidelines.  
In case of conflicts in interpretation between this privacy policy and guideline of each service, the guideline of each service shall prevail.

### RANGE OF PROTECTION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

The information that livedoor collect in order to provide services to users will be protected under livedoor Privacy Policy.  
But for the information that user enters outside of our web sites as a result of leaving our web sites following links or ads on our web sites is out of our range of protection.

### Private information refers to

  * Name, Zip code, Address, Telephone Number, Date of birth
  * ID, Password, Mail Address, IP, Telephone number, Communication history
  * Credit card information, Pay information, Non-payment history

### PURPOSE OF USING PERSONAL INFORMATION

The purposes of using users' personal information collected from Our Service are followings

  * To improve Our Service and to maintain Our system effectively
  * To introduce new commodity, service, campaign, or gift from livedoor to users
  * To notify publicity, maintenance and important news to users
  * To send direct mail or FAX on goods and services of partner companies that are considered to be useful to users
  * To ship goods or services to customers
  * For marketing activities of goods or services that livedoor and our partner companies offer.

When a user requests a change, revision, or cancellation on our service, livedoor will handle the request without hesitation after checking the identification of the user.

### THE WAY OF OBTAINING PERSONAL INFORMATION

### Obtaining information directly

livedoor will obtain personal information in fair way and will never obtain such information contrary to user's will. To do so, livedoor will either ask for acceptance from a user for the purposes of information gathering or notify necessary information on our web site. 

### Obtaining information indirectly

livedoor will check whether personal information has been obtained in appropriate ways. livedoor will announce necessary statements on the purposes of the use of personal information on our web site after signing contract with suppliers of such information.

### TO RELEASE PERSONAL INFORMATION TO OTHER PARTIES

livedoor will not disclose or release a user's personal information to other parties without approval from the user. In case of releasing personal information to other parties for tie-up or outsourcing, livedoor will investigate allied companies and make necessary contract such as non-disclosure agreement in order to manage personal information appropriately.

### DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

livedoor will not disclose personal information of users except for

  * Releasing information that is extracted from the analysis of statistics that cannot be used to identify particular individuals.
  * Consent of disclosure of personal information from the user.
  * Order of disclosure of personal information from the court of law.
  * Request of disclosure of personal information from prosecution of police and authorities in legal ways.
  * Claim of disclosure of personal information based on laws.

### PROCEDURE OF CORRECTION, SUSPENSION AND ELIMINATION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

Whenever a user requests to disclose, correct, suspend, or eliminate personal information, or to cancel our service, livedoor will process the request after checking the identification of the user.  
To request cancellation of service, please proceed following link. 

  * Fastladder resign

### LAW OF PERSONAL INFORMATION PROTECTION

### Range of personal information

Personal information management will be done only by authorized personnel of livedoor.

### Prohibited uses of personal information

  * livedoor will not use personal information other than designated purposes. livedoor will take all actions to prevent personal information from leaking out such as getting data out or sending data to others.
  * livedoor will obligate all employees to keep confidential information both while and after the employment.
  * livedoor will not obtain, use, or release personal information regarding following matters.

Information that relates to social discrimination such as though, religion, race, nationality, disability, mental disorder, criminal record, health/medical treatment, sex life, and social/political activities.

### EXEMPTION OF LIABILITY

livedoor will not manage a user ID and password for each user.  
Insecure management of user ID and password may allow access to your registered personal information. Please be responsible and cautioned for your own information management.

### OTHERS

livedoor will do our best continuously in terms of users' personal information protection making necessary updates to our services and policies. Updates will be announced on this page whenever necessary.

2007.7.2 (Last Updated)  
livedoor Co.,Ltd.  
Takeshi IDEZAWA, CEO
